I scaled a business from here to here fast.
So this was the business' numbers beforehand.
So every 100 appointments booked,
49% of people were showing up,
and out of those, 83% were actually being offered.
And out of those, only 27% closed.
And from that, only 47% paid.
And so the units sold the prior month
in this business was 56.
This business had five problems that we had to solve.
So problem number one was show up rate.
So they were optimizing
for the lowest cost of leads and appointments.
So we had them hire a new media buyer
and adjust the optimization towards lowest cost per sale
rather than per lead.
Also, we had their status go from doing this
Number two was close rate.
It was too low.
So during the discovery at the beginning of the sales call,
they were asking service level questions.
So we optimized the sales script
and helped them create more questions
to really understand why the prospect was there
so they could sell them easier
and then ultimately get them less objections
in the close at the end of the sale.
Number three was the people and org structure.
So their team had three parts,
a sales manager, closers, and setters.
Number one, the sales manager.
The CEO was a sales manager.
He's a great closer, but not a great sales manager.
So he hired a sales director,
who had been a sales trainer for a similar type sale before.
Number two, closers.
We reduced the closing team because they had too many.
And so we cut the lowest percentage salespeople on the team
and we kept the best ones.
Number three was setters.
So we downsized the setting team and increased expectations
because the setters expectations were way too low.
After implementing all these changes, here were the results.
So business owners,
if you want to scale your business like this,
zero promises whatsoever.
Most people do nothing,
but you can comment map for a free personalized scaling
roadmap, just help you out.